Guide to the Ian R. MacNeil papers, 1975-1978.
MacNeil, Ian R. papers, 1975-1978.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Ian R. MacNeil papers, 1975-1978.
18-2-1877
Ian R. MacNeil
2 cubic ft.
Correspondence, corporate studies, clippings
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes files of Ian R. MacNeil relating to Cerrache T.V. (Ithaca, New York) and the Tompkins County Cable Commission; also, files of the Director of the 1975 Priorities Study concerning academic and administrative goals at Cornell University.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Ian Roderick MacNeil, born 1929; professor of law, Cornell University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes files of Ian R. MacNeil relating to Cerrache T.V. (Ithaca, New York) and the Tompkins County Cable Commission; also, files of the Director of the 1975 Priorities Study concerning academic and administrative goals at Cornell University.
SUBJECTS
Names:
MacNeil, Ian R.; Cerrache T.V.; Cornell University--Administration.; Cornell University--Planning.; Cornell University. Priorities Study.; Tompkins County Cable Commission.
Subjects:
Cable television.; College teachers.
Places:
Tompkins County (N.Y.)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Cornell University Reports
  - Program Budget Reviews, 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Program Budget Reviews, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - "An Overview of Two Recent Surveys of Administrative Computer Operations in Higher Education"-Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Report of the Trustee Ad Hoc Committee on Capital Financing, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Summary of Administrative Data Processing Including Expenditures - Fiscal Years 1971-75, 1971-1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Comparable Institutional Data Survey: Some Observations, Nov1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Comparable Institutional Data Survey: Some Observations, Nov.1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Comparable Insitutitonal Data, April 1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Comparable Institutional Data Survey, June 1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Cornell Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Cornell Budget-Supporting Data and Narrative, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Factual Profile of Cornell University, Feb. 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11A)
  - Cornell in the Seventies - Goals, Priorities and Plans, May 1973 (Box 1, Folder 11B)
  - Cornell in the Seventies - Background Information and Studies, May 1973 (Box 1, Folder 11C)
  - Report of the Personnel Study Committee, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 11D)
  - Report of the Faculty Committee on the Quality of Undergraduate Instruction, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 11E)
  - Report of the Ad Hoc Committee on University Financial Planning, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 11F)
  - Report of the Ad Hoc Trustee Committee on the Status of Women, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11G)
  - Report of the Health Planning Steering Committee, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 11H)
  - Appendices for the Report of the Health Planning Steering Committee-vol. II, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 11I)
- Series II. Priorities Study done by the University in 1975
  - Memoranda to Task Force Chairmen, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Final reports - Corson, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - Corson, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence -David Knapp, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Cranch Report - Committee Reports, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Support Ratios, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - Macneil, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Organizational charts, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - Sol Linowitz, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence - Samuel Lawrence, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Corson letter-deteriorating financial scene, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Priorities Study - Report to the Director, June 1975 (Box 1)
  - Priorities Study - Task Force #1-3, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Priorities Study - Task Force #3-8, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Priorities Study - Task Force #9-16, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Priorities Study - Task Force #18-27, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence concerning the Priorities Study, 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 1-6)
  - Senate- Summer Study Group Report, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Self Study Law Faculty, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Cornell-Space Utilization Study, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Editorial by Macneil for Daily Sun; Correspondence by Macneil and Corson, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence from Corson; Report of the Coordinator of the Social Sciences Task Forces, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Preliminary Report of the President's Commission on Self-Governance, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Series III. Tompkins County Cable Commission
  - Reports, Memos, Correspondence, etc. concerning the cable franchise, 1974-1979 (Box 2, Folder 13-18)
  - Grant of franchise - Ceracche TV Corp (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper clippings concerning the franchise, 1970s (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - American Television and Communications Corporation, 1977 (Box 2)